(Alfred:)How is everyone today?
(Beverley:)Good, and you?
(Alfred:)Good, good.
Good.
(Mary:)I'm good, too.
(Randall (Penny's brother):)Good.
(Sheldon:)So, did you defile
my mother or not?
Sheldon!
(Mary:)You're being rude.
(Alfred:)If I may, I can assure you,
(Alfred:)your mother and I
did nothing more
(Alfred:)than share a cab
and a conversation.
(Sheldon:)Did that conversation
include the phrase
"your genitals
are a joy to behold"?
That's enough!
(Alfred:)Look, I promise you, neither I,
nor anyone, has ever said that.
(Leonard:)You don't know his girlfriend
very well.
(Sheldon:)Or what a joy it is
to behold my genitals.
(Penny:)All right, you guys, uh,
get settled in,
(Penny:)then we'll go across the hall
and say hi to everyone.
(Randall:)You know, It's hard to believe
I've never met Leonard.
(Wyatt:)Well, he probably buys
his illegal drugs
(Wyatt:)from a local vendor.
(Susan:)Not funny, Wyatt.
(Penny:)I thought it was really funny.
Thanks.